Guide to the Terri Hendrix Accessions
The Wittliff Collections
Terri Hendrix Accessions
1982-2007
The Wittliff Collections https://www.thewittliffcollections.txstate.edu
Hendrix, Terri
UPWC.18033
25 Linear Feet
28 boxes
The archive of musician Terri Hendrix includes correspondence, photographs, programs and flyers, awards, articles about Hendrix, composition notebooks, lyrics, sheet music, recordings, artifacts, and posters. Correspondence includes greeting cards, letters, and fan mail – many from young students. Awards includes her 2016 induction into the San Marcos Women's Hall of Fame and contains the nomination packet put together by Richard Skanse. The recordings are arranged by format: 2" reel studio recordings - many produced by Lloyd Maines; audiocassettes of demos, live performances, and recordings spanning 1989-2007; CDs of the same spanning 1997-2015; DAT tapes; and mini discs. The collection also includes VHS cassettes and computer files, and a pair of painted overalls worn by Hendrix while performing.
Conditions Governing Access
Collection is open for research.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Terri Hendrix, 2018
Scope and Contents
The archive of musician Terri Hendrix includes correspondence, photographs, programs and flyers, awards, articles about Hendrix, composition notebooks, lyrics, sheet music, recordings, artifacts, and posters. Correspondence includes greeting cards, letters, and fan mail – many from young students. Awards includes her 2016 induction into the San Marcos Women's Hall of Fame and contains the nomination packet put together by Richard Skanse. The recordings are arranged by format: 2" reel studio recordings - many produced by Lloyd Maines; audiocassettes of demos, live performances, and recordings spanning 1989-2007; CDs of the same spanning 1997-2015; DAT tapes; and mini discs. The collection also includes VHS cassettes and computer files, and a pair of painted overalls worn by Hendrix while performing.
Index Terms
Subjects
Women musicians; Songs -- Texts; Americana (Music); Popular music -- Writing and publishing; Music -- Performance
Subjects (Persons)
Hendrix, Terri; Maines, Lloyd
- Accession 2018-033
  Abstract
  The archive of musician Terri Hendrix includes correspondence, photographs, programs and flyers, awards, articles about Hendrix, composition notebooks, lyrics, sheet music, recordings, artifacts, and posters. Correspondence includes greeting cards, letters, and fan mail – many from young students. Awards includes her 2016 induction into the San Marcos Women's Hall of Fame and contains the nomination packet put together by Richard Skanse. The recordings are arranged by format: 2" reel studio recordings - many produced by Lloyd Maines; audiocassettes of demos, live performances, and recordings spanning 1989-2007; CDs of the same spanning 1997-2015; DAT tapes; and mini discs. The collection also includes VHS cassettes and computer files, and a pair of painted overalls worn by Hendrix while performing.
  - Personal papers (vision statement; possible 4th grade composition, medical information sheet) (Box 2736, Folder 1)
  - Inspirational sayings (clippings, post-it notes) (Box 2736, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence (general letters, notes, email print-outs) (Box 2736, Folder 3-4)
  - Greeting cards (Box 2736, Folder 5-9)
  - Children's letters and cards to veterans (Box 2736, Folder 10)
  - Fan mail – military (includes letter with 2 Iraqi dinars enclosed) (Box 2736, Folder 11)
  - Fan mail - students (Box 2736, Folder 12-14)
  - Photographs (primarily snapshots, digital print-outs) (Box 2736, Folder 15)
  - Performance flyers, programs (Box 2736, Folder 16)
  - Performance – Smithsonian Folklife Festival, 2008 (Box 2736, Folder 17)
  - Performance set lists, backstage signs (Box 2736, Folder 18)
  - Awards – San Marcos Women's Hall of Fame (includes Richard Skanse nomination, programs, speech) (Box 2736, Folder 19)
  - Awards – Austin Music Awards, "Best Folk Band," 1999-2000 (Box 2736, Folder 20)
  - Awards – Austin Music Awards, "Best Folk Act," 2000-2001 (Box 2736, Folder 21)
  - Cry Till You Laugh: The Part That Ain't Art (6 copies) (Box 2736)
  - Music
    - Composition books – Liturgical music, guitar (2 books) (Box 2737, Folder 1)
    - Composition books – "Bocetos musicales de las cabras 1" (Box 2737, Folder 2)
    - Composition books – "2" illustrated front page "A Fine Mess" (Box 2737, Folder 3)
    - Composition books – "3", July 15, 1990 (Box 2737, Folder 4)
    - Composition books – "4", March 21, 1991 (Box 2737, Folder 5)
    - "Ideas" folders (lyrics, chord sheets, sheet music) (Box 2737, Folder 6-7)
    - Loose compositions (Box 2737, Folder 8)
    - Notebook with lyrics and chords (Box 2737, Folder 9)
    - Notebook, "The Spiritual Kind: Lloyd's book", 2007 (Box 2737, Folder 10)
    - Music folder – "Terri's Lessons," and a SWT folder with sheet music (Box 2737, Folder 11)
    - Music folder– Interoffice envelope with sheet music "M. Johnston" (Box 2737, Folder 12)
    - Music folder– "Mass for the King of Glory – Paulkingham," "Folk Mass," and Mariachi Marbecke – Spanish Mass" (Box 2737, Folder 13)
    - Music folder – "S. and Hymns", 1982 (Box 2737, Folder 14)
    - Music folder – "Guitar Duets," and "Gariboldi Copies" (Box 2737, Folder 15)
    - Music folder – "Guitar and Piano," "Guitar and Piano Diabelli," and "R. Straube Harpsichord and Guitar" (Box 2737, Folder 16)
    - Music folder – "N. Coste oboe and Guitar" (2 folders) (Box 2737, Folder 17)
    - Loose sheet music (Box 2737, Folder 18)
    - Instruction books (Box 2737, Folder 19)
    - Published sheet music, various (Box 2737, Folder 20)
    - Country All-Timers, 60 Songs Best in Country and Top Country Hits of 1977 (Box 2737, Folder 21)
    - Traditional, Country, and Electric Slide Guitar (Box 2737, Folder 22)
    - The Great Songs of George Gershwin (Box 2737, Folder 23)
  - Publications
    - Julien's Auction, Gibson, 2007 (Box 2738)
    - Texas Singer-Songwriters Photographs by Gary Goldberg (2 copies) (Box 2738, Item 2)
    - Texas Music w/ Hendrix on cover, Fall 2007 (Box 2738, Item 3)
    - Texas Music, Spring 2012 (Box 2738, Item 4)
    - Lone Star Music Magazine, June/July 2010 (Box 2738, Item 5)
    - Lone Star Music Magazine, January/February 2013 (Box 2738, Item 6)
    - Various articles and newspapers featuring Hendrix (Box 2738, Item 7)
  - 2" Open Reel Studio Recordings, 1995
    - Horizon Recording Studio (3 reels with recording sheets), May 19, 1995 (Box 2739)
    - "Flowers" and "Walk on Me" Fire Station Studio, Lloyd Maines Producer (1 reel with 2 recording sheets), September 8, 1997 (Box 2740)
    - "Terri Hendrix Transfers," "Waiting on a Train" (1 reel), October 1997 (Box 2740)
    - "Terri Hendrix 1 Transfer", October, 1998 (Box 2740)
    - "Terri H." transfers of September 8, 1997 recordings (3 reels, sheets with reel 3), October 1, 1998 (Box 2741)
    - "Terri Hendrix," Cedar Creek Recording, Lloyd Maines, Producer (2 reels, sheets in reel 2), November - December, 1999 (Box 2742)
    - "Terri H 2" loose reel, undated (Box 2742)
    - "Terri Hendrix 2002" Cedar Creek Recording, Lloyd Maines, Producer (2 reels, sheets with reel 1), January - February, 2002 (Box 2743)
    - "Terri Hendrix Transfers," loose reel, undated (Box 2743)
  - Audiocassettes - Demos, 1992, undated
    - "First Demo" (Box 2744)
    - "Demos" (Box 2744)
    - "Old Demo at Ace's" (Box 2744)
    - "Demo of Originals" (2 tapes) (Box 2744)
    - "Demo #2 / Demo #3" (Box 2744)
    - "Demo Tape" (Box 2744)
    - "Various TH Original Demos" (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Demo" (Box 2744)
    - "Demo for Lloyd [Maines]" (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix" (Box 2744)
    - "Demo" (Box 2744)
    - "Gruene Hall Demo" (Box 2744)
    - "Master Demo", 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Rick Stockton's Studio Demo", June 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Demo #6", September 26, 1992 (Box 2744)
  - Audiocassettes, 1989
    - "Marion Williamson – audition" (Box 2744)
  - Audiocassettes, 1990
    - "Partier Do Tí Mí ", May 24, 1990 (Box 2744)
    - "MW '90", July 9, 1990; August 11, 1990 (Box 2744)
    - "MW", August 11, 1990, September 30, 1990, November 9, 1990 (Box 2744)
    - "Hollow Men – reh" (2 tapes), November, 1990 (Box 2744)
    - "Mysterium", November 12, 1990 (Box 2744)
    - "Vocal Tape" (Box 2744)
  - Audiocassettes, 1991
    - "Terri and Grant", February 2, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Katy", August 30, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Live Hendrix", August 3, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Live at Katy", September 27, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Katy", October 11, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Katy", October 25, 1991 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Katy", November 15, 1991 (Box 2744)
  - Audiocassettes, 1992
    - "Terri Prac[tice]", January 3, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at the Elbow Room: Sets 1 & 2", February 8, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - Terri Hendrix Live at the Elbow Room: Set 3", February 8, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at the Elbow Room: Short Sets, Frat Party (verbal abuse)", February 8, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix – Leon Springs: Sets 1 & 2", February 21, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix – Leon Springs: Set 3", February 21, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix – High Time", February 29, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix – Demo Master", March 4, 1992
    - "Terri Hendrix – High Time: Sets 1 & 2", March 7, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix – High Time: Set 3", March 7, 1992
    - "Master 'Pink Room'", April 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "R-12 Café", May 9, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "KFAN 107.9 FM Dr. John Scott with guest Terri Hendrix", July 25, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Hollow Men, counterpoint", November 29, 1992 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Oonies", December 12, 1992 (Box 2744)
  - Audiocassettes, 1993
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Oonies" January 30, 1993 (Box 2744)
    - "Rick Stockton Mixes", February 1993 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix", July 27, 1993 (Box 2744)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live at Oonies", July 27, 1993 (Box 2745)
    - "Cantisani", 1993 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 1994
    - "Jacks Job Studio 16", 1994 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri's Tape", April 15, 1995 (Box 2745)
    - "Sunday Night Session", November 26, 1995 (Box 2745)
    - "Vocal Tapes", 1995 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 1996
    - "KSTX's Sunday Nite Session 1ith Jim Volk", March 10, 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix and Jim Volk Live at Gruene Hall", June 6, 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix Radio Interview", August 4, 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Sunday Night Session – Terri Hendrix", October 27, 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Live Set Studio 1A", 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Jim Volk et al", 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Jim Volk", 1996 (Box 2745)
    - "Mix 96 Folk Soul" (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 1997
    - "Ray Rickland and I" (2 tapes), March 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "KIND Radio", April 15, 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "Woodcreek", May 4, 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "Master Copy Gruene Hall and etc.", May 1997 (Box 2745)
    - Terri Hendrix – 3rd Coast Music Network – Velvet Jones", August 11, 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "Live Set", August 17, 1997 (Box 2745)
    - Humble Time Show #36, feature artist Ray Wylie Hubbard", August 23, 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "Guitar Vocal", 1997 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix", 1997 (Box 2745)
    - KGSR, June 19, 1997 / "Live at Texas Summer Nights," March 8, 1998 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 1998
    - "New Years", 1998-1999 (Box 2745)
    - "Poor David's (Lloyd and I)", September 19, 1998 (Box 2745)
    - "KLBJ with Lloyd", October 1998 (Box 2745)
    - "Betty Elders", October 23 1998 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri's Band", November 6, 1998 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri and Band", November 6, 1998 (Box 2745)
    - "Lloyd and I Live", 1998 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 1999
    - "John Hadley Songs", February 1999 (Box 2745)
    - "World Café", July 15, 1999 (Box 2745)
    - "BBC Production: Bob Harris Country including sessions with Ray Wylie Hubbard and Terri Hendrix", November 4, 1999 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 2000
    - "KLBJ Dudley and Bob", June 5, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri / Lloyd, Tin Angel", June 8, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Gruene Hall", June 23, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Cheatham Street Warehouse", September 30, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Hill Country Hayride with Terri and Lloyd", November 24, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix, Cheatham Street", December 31, 2000 (Box 2745)
    - "Glenn Meganck", 2000 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 2001
    - "T.H. Berges Fest", June 15, 2001 (Box 2745)
    - Terri Hendrix and Lloyd Maines. WLUW 88.7 Chicago", June 2001 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix and Lloyd Maines Live at Henflings", August 21, 2001 (Box 2745)
    - "McCabe's Concerts, Darryl Purpose", September 6, 2001 (Box 2745)
    - "John Hadley Songs for Terri", November 2001 (Box 2745)
    - "San Marcos", 2001 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 2002
    - Untitled (2 tapes), January 26, 2002 (Box 2745)
    - "Terri Hendrix, Tin Angel", March 15, 2002 (Box 2745)
    - "Millsaps Arts & Lecture Series Poets of the Heart: Suzanne Buirgy and Terri Hendrix" (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 2003
    - "Steve and Johnnie" [I label], October 8, 2003 (Box 2745)
    - "Inspiration", 2003 (Box 2745)
  - Audiocassettes, 2004
    - "Vocal", February 8, 2004 (Box 2746)
    - "Vocal", April 28, 2004 (Box 2746)
  - Audiocassettes, 2006
    - "Terri Hendrix", 2006 (Box 2746)
  - Audiocassettes, 2007
    - "New Tunes 07 Stuff", 2007 (Box 2746)
  - Audiocassettes (51 tapes), undated (Box 2746)
  - Audiocassettes (19 tapes), undated (Box 2747)
  - Audiocassettes (9 tapes), undated (Box 2748)
  - Produced Tapes, undated
    - Hill Country Songwriters Special, Vol 1 (4 copies) (Box 2748)
    - The Best of Nina Simone (Box 2748)
    - Rain Town, Deacon Blue (Box 2748)
    - The Original Al Barlow (Box 2748)
    - Jane Gillman (Box 2748)
    - Distant Visions (Box 2748)
  - CDs - Live recordings and interviews, 1997-2015
    - Ace's, March 1997 (Box 2749)
    - Untitled, October 12, 1997 (Box 2749)
    - "Terri Hendrix Live!", April 1998 (Box 2749)
    - Live at Texas Summer Nights w/ Lloyd Maines, March 6, 1999 (Box 2749)
    - Interview (airdate August 11, 1999), July 15, 1999 (Box 2749)
    - Untitled, December 29, 1999 (Box 2749)
    - Cibolo, 1999 (Box 2749)
    - Meridian Live w/ Larry Joe Taylor, 1999 (Box 2749)
    - KGSR in the AM, April 1, 2000 (Box 2749)
    - Waterloo Records, May 4, 2000 / Cibolo Creek, May 19, 2000 (Box 2749)
    - World Café hosted by David Dye. w/ Lloyd Maines, June 8, 2000 (Box 2749)
    - Old No. 9 Music Series w/ Lloyd Maines (student performances), 2000 (Box 2749)
    - Live at WLUW Chicago. w/ Lloyd Maines, 2000-2001 (Box 2749)
    - Strings, February 21, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Strings "J label", February 26, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - KGSR at the Four Seasons. SXSW, March 15, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Hill Country Stage, April 6, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - WNCW-FM w/ Lloyd Maines "A" label, April 26, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival, June 2001 (Box 2749)
    - "Strings" Sets 1 & 2, August 22, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Four Corners Folk Festival, August 31, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Ed's House, Altadera, CA w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), November 4, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Thursday Armadillo (2 copies), November 18, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - Meadowfest w/ Lloyd Maines and Frog Holler, 2001 (Box 2749)
    - "Terry Hendrix at Godfrey Daniels "L" label, March 14, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - WDIY-FM w/ Lloyd Maines "N" label, March 14, 2002 and October 2, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - At Godfrey Daniels (2 discs) "L" label, March 14, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Live at Poor David's Pub, Dallas, March 30, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Hill Country Stage, Driftwood, Texas, April 20, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - KUT-FM Eklektikos, Live Studio 1-A, June 4, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Ring Around the Radio, KUT (Box 2749)
    - KERA-FM, Dallas. David Okanoto, July 17, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Four Corners Folk Festival, Pagosa Springs, CO, August 31, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Silverton Festival, CO, August 31, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - ECM Building, Lawrence, KS w/ Lloyd Maines, September 22, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - At Godfrey Daniels (2 discs) "M" and "O" labels, October 3, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Live at Texana Grill, October 6, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Strings Sets 1 & 2 (2 discs), November 6, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Kuumbwa Jazz Center, Santa Cruz, CA w/ Lloyd Maines, November 8, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Texas Nights Concerts w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), November 17, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Texas Nights Concerts w/ Lloyd Maines "B" label, November 17, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - KUT-FM Live Studio 1-A, December 10, 2002 (Box 2749)
    - Live Set, January 5, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - Cactus Café w/ Lloyd Maines (DVD) (2 copies), February 8, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - Café Fantastique w/ Lloyd Maines "F" label, Spring 2003 (Box 2749)
    - Thrasher Opera House, May 10, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - Thrasher Opera House Raw CD "E" label, May 10, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - Interview w/ Lloyd Maines (airdate September 23, 2003), July 7, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - World Café w/ Lloyd Maines, July 7, 2003 (Box 2749)
    - "Pre edit XM Radio" 2/ Lloyd Maines, July 11, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Cactus Café, July 19, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Texas Theatre, August 8, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - "Live at Pilot's Grill" (2 disks) w/ Lloyd Maines, October 5, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Live After Dark, Steve & Johnnie. w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), October 8, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Live at the Ark, October 10, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - TNC w/ Lloyd Maines (4 disks), October 18, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - PSB "G" label, November 8, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - w/ Lloyd Maines (2 disks), November 12, 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Old No. 9 Music Series w/ Lloyd Maines (student performances), 2003 (Box 2750)
    - Sony Circle Concert, Pasadena, CA w/ Lloyd Maines; David [Francey], Dave Clarke, Tim Grimm (2 copies), February 29, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - CSPS, Cedar Rapids, IA w/ Lloyd Maines, May 15, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - The Glenn Mitchell Show, June 3, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - Live at McGonigel's Mucky Duck w/ Lloyd Maines, June 18, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - Texas Union Theatre, June 19, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - Live at the Ark, September 11, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - TNC w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), September 25, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), October 29, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - Live at Casa Undici, Piedmont, CA, November 6, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - At the Duck [McGonigel's Mucky Duck] ( 2 parts), December 10, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - County Line. DND Performance, 2004 (Box 2750)
    - KUHT Houston PBS (2 copies), 2004 (Box 2750)
    - Old No. 9 Music Series w/ Lloyd Maines (student performances), 2004 (Box 2750)
    - KXCI Tucson, March 11, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Live at Mountain Stage, April 3, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Glenn Mitchell Show, KERA 90.1, Dallas w/ Lloyd Maines, May 20, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Corsicana, TX (DVD), May 28, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival, June 4, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - San Marcos (TX) River Pub, July 10, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Silverton (CO) Summer Jubilee Live mix (days 1 & 2), Summer 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Live on KSYM, San Antonio w/ Lloyd Maines, August 26, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - San Marcos (TX) River Pub, September 10, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - TNC w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), October 8, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - Lake City Wine Fest, 2005 (Box 2750)
    - KUT Eklektikos, Live from Studio 1-A, February 23, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Fox Run Concert (2 copies), April 15, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Fox Run "The Ring" (2 copies), April 15, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Live at the Ark w/ Lloyd Maines, May 18, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Tin Angel, Philadelphia (2 discs), June 29, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - San Marcos (TX) River Pub, Father's Day, June 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Eddie's Attic, September 22, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Spam & Grits, Atlanta 89.3, September 22, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - WFMT's Folkstage w/ Lloyd Maines, October 21, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - WFMT's Folkstage w/ Lloyd Maines. Disc 1 (2 copies), October 21, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - WFMT's Folkstage w/ Lloyd Maines Disc 2, October 21, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Midnight Special WFMT w/ Lloyd Maines (3 parts), October 21, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Live at the Bugle Boy, La Grange, October 28, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Live Oak Coffee House, November 10, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Live at Lucy's Boat yard ME Television (DVD) (2 copies), 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Tucson Folk Festival, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - Fox Run, 2006 (Box 2750)
    - w/ Lloyd Maines, April 19, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Evening Star, April 29, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - "Spiritual Kind" bootlegs, June 14, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Compilation of live recordings, June 18, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - X Country, XM Satellite Radio w/ Lloyd Maines, July 20, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Club Helsinki w/ Lloyd Maines, July 25, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - KUT, Live from Studio 1-A (2 copies), August 30, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - KSTX, Texas Public Radio w/ Lloyd Maines, September 7, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - KBUT Interview w/ Lloyd Maines, September 18, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - McDavid Studio, Fort Worth (2 discs), September 28, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Live in Sty w/ Lloyd Maines, November 8, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - The Midnight Special, WFMT w/ Lloyd Maines (2 discs), December 31, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Floore's Country Store, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Terri H. Bootlegs, 2007 (Box 2751)
    - Live at Bend Studio (2 discs), February 1, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - w/ Lloyd Maines, April 10, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Soundcheck Texas, Program #SCT112, April 18-20, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - WAMU Folklife Music for Fireworks w/ Lloyd Maines (2 copies), July 4, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Summer in the Park, July 5, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Live at Lakeside Icehouse w/ Lloyd Maines (2 discs), August 15, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - KUT Folkways, Austin w/ Lloyd Maines, August 16, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - WT BK & Music Fest w/ Lloyd Maines, September 26, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Freight (2 discs), October 14, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Kim Rogers interview, KYMR 89.5 w/ Lloyd Maines, October 16, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - LAS Live, First week, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - LAS Live, Second week, 2008 (Box 2751)
    - Third Coast Theatre, February 6, 2009 (Box 2751)
    - Berklee College of Music clinic w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies), April 2, 2009, 2pm (Box 2751)
    - Berklee College of Music clinic w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies), April 2, 2009, 8pm (Box 2751)
    - [Daniel], Terri & Lloyd, April 10, 2009 (Box 2751)
    - The Red Dragon, Baton Rouge, LA (3 discs), April 25, 2009 (Box 2751)
    - Live at the Kerrville Folk Festival w/Lloyd Maines (2 copies), May 2009 (Box 2751)
    - Live at McDavid Studio, Fort Worth w/Lloyd Maines and Slaid Cleaves (2 discs), December 11, 2009 (Box 2751)
    - Fox Run (2 discs), 2009 (Box 2751)
    - KUT Eklektikos, Studio 1-A w/Lloyd Maines (2 discs), February 10, 2010 (Box 2751)
    - Live on Wildman Steve Radio, May 7, 2010 (Box 2751)
    - Wildflower, Eisemann Center, Richardson, TX w/Lloyd Maines, May 16, 2010 (Box 2751)
    - Live Oak Music Festival, Santa Barbara, CA w/Lloyd Maines, June 18-20, 2010 (Box 2751)
    - St. Mary's University, San Antonio. 2010 Art of Peace Award (2 copies) (Box 2751)
    - Woody Fest, 2010 (Box 2751)
    - Living Legends, Price Center, San Marcos, TX, May 26, 2011 (Box 2751)
    - KPLG w/Lloyd Maines, July 24, 2011 (Box 2751)
    - KUT Eklektikos 2/ Lloyd Maines, September 14, 2011 (Box 2751)
    - Kerrville Folk Festival, June 3, 2012 (Box 2751)
    - Cactus Café, Austin, TX, February 15, 2013 (Box 2751)
    - San Antonio, TX (2 discs), March 22, 2013 (Box 2751)
    - Wildflower, Richardson Arts & Music Festival w/Lloyd Maines, May 17-19. 2013 (Box 2751)
    - Bugle Boy Live Performance Collection (Briscoe Center), LaGrange, TX, 2013 (Box 2751)
    - KOOP 91.7, Austin w/Lloyd Maines, February 5, 2014 (Box 2751)
    - Cultural Activities Center, Temple, Texas w/Lloyd Maines, October 11, 2014 (Box 2751)